## Sebastian Casallas Arias

Colombia, Bogotá · https://www.linkedin.com/in/sebastian-casallas-arias-a46645302 · +57 3224729356 · sebastiancasallasarias2020@gmail.com

**Junior Software Developer** with over 6 months of experience in Full Stack development. I have worked on projects such as SASS platforms for veterinarians and team management using technologies like Node.js, Express, React, and TailwindCSS. I excel in implementing clean code architectures and strict typing, ensuring software quality and scalability. Additionally, I can communicate in Spanish and a strong passion for continuous learning.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Zecsba – APV**FullStack Developer

May – 2024 – July 2024

- Developed a platform to manage patients for each veterinarian in the area.
- Implemented Model View Controller using Node.js and Express, improving code readability.
- Utilized React and TailwindCSS for Frontend development.

Zecsba - UpTask

FullStack Developer

Colombia, Bogotá

June – 2024 – August 2024

- Developed a platform for team management for small and medium-sized companies in the sector.
- Implemented strict typing for both Backend and Frontend to avoid execution errors.

**Academlo - Ecommerce** 

FrontEnd Developer

Colombia, Bogotá

June – 2024 – June 2024

- Developed a virtual store with authentication for purchasing items.
- Used React for the Frontend.
- I also developed the API which is being consumed in the project.

## **EDUCATION**

Academlo

Colombia, Bogotá

March 2024

FullStack Developer

Milestones Education Course Intensive English

Australia, Melbourne

January 2023 - March 2024

## ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- **Technical Skills:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Express, TailwindCSS, clean code architecture, strict typing.
- **Soft Skills:** Time management, teamwork, effective communication, adaptability, flexibility, self-learning, Leadership.